Partial Register of the Boris N. Volkov Papers, 1915-1963
Hoover Institution Archives
- Microfilm of the Boris N. Volkov Papers held at the Museum of Russian Culture (Reel 1-23)
  - Photographs, c. 1915-1950. (Box 20)
    - Ten photographs include one of Volkov, taken probably during the First World War, three of Russian translators and interpreters working for the United Nations, and the rest of unidentified people and places (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Oversize File, 1921-1963 (Box 21)
    Scrapbooks containing biographical material and writings, as well as oversize writings, arranged alphabetically by physical form
    - Scrapbooks
      - Biographical material. Contains brief biography of Volkov by unidentified individual, clippings (Volkov's poems and articles as well as information about him), correspondence, autographed poems, photograph World War I period), 1963 February 2, (undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
      - Clippings I. Newspaper articles (by and about Volkov) and Volkov's poems. Includes draft of "Predel" (See SPEECHES AND WRITINGS for other draft), 1921-1933 (Folder 3)
      - Clippings II. Poems (and one short story), 1925-1937 (Folder 4)
    - Writings. "Severo-vostochnyi ugol Pekina," Background materials, notes and typescript. Includes correspondence and documents relating to the Russian Orthodox Mission in Peking (Folder 5-6)